[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these characters was Obi-Wan Kenobis mentor?", "correct_answer": "Qui Gon Jin", "incorrect_answers": ["Mace Windu", "Yoda", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A rodents teeth will grow continuously for its entire lifetime.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Not Ready For Primetime Players debuted on Saturday Night Live in 1975. Which of these was not part of the original cast?", "correct_answer": "Jim Belushi", "incorrect_answers": ["Garrett Morris", "Jane Curtin", "Chevy Chase"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Rough Collie was awarded a star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame?", "correct_answer": "Lassie", "incorrect_answers": ["Odie", "Honey", "Beauty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the age difference between Barbie and her boyfriend Ken.", "correct_answer": "2 years", "incorrect_answers": ["3 years", "4 years", "1 year"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "1971s The French Connection was the first R-rated movie to win the Academy Award for Best Picture since the introduction of the MPAA film rating system.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He wrote the screenplay for Batman Begins (2005), but hes probably more famous for writing the Blade movies (Blade, Blade II, and Blade: Trinity).", "correct_answer": "David S. Goyer", "incorrect_answers": ["Shinobu Hashimoto", "David Benioff", "Joss Whedon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete this famous quotation, attributed to, and denied by, Winston Churchill. \nDont talk to me about naval tradition. Its nothing but ____, sodomy, and the lash.", "correct_answer": "Rum", "incorrect_answers": ["Ropes", "Rashes", "Rotten biscuits"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How does Paulinas grandson describe Paulinas house to Darrin in the 2003 comedy The Fighting Temptations?", "correct_answer": "As a no-point-of-living-at-all house", "incorrect_answers": ["As the-paradise-on-earth house", "As a nice place which can use some grandma cleaning", "As the house of the Devil herself"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor is the first one  to win 10 Razzies.", "correct_answer": "Sylvester Stallone", "incorrect_answers": ["Kevin Costner", "Andrew Dice Clay", "Rob Lowe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What make and model car does Garth own in the Waynes World movie?", "correct_answer": "AMC Pacer", "incorrect_answers": ["Buick Park Ave.", "Lincoln Continental", "Ford Escort"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 2009 song was featured in the trailer and TV spots of the comedy movie The Ugly Truth?", "correct_answer": "Right Round by Flo Rida", "incorrect_answers": ["So Fine by Sean Paul", "Warning/Tornado by Rihanna", "Work by Ciara ft. Missy Elliott"]}]